And then after you've prepared your tape grid the next step you want to do is add some greenery to cover up your mechanics and add prepare a foundation for your arrangement.
So you want to cut the greenery and tuck it in between the grid holes like this.
And you can add, this is leather leaf.
Just tick it in like that.
Make sure it's getting down into the water.
And you're going to put a couple of pieces, it doesn't have to be completely full.
And this is how you edge your greenery.
Just like that.
And then we'll take, this is lemon leaves.
It'll add a different texture and a fullness.
Again, cutting your stems before you put them down into the water.
Cut the stems, place it in.
And you just want to create, your hydrangeas are going to be up here so you just want to create a good foundation.
And that'll hold them securely in the bowl between the grid and your greenery.
So we're just going to put a few more pieces in like this and we're going to go around in a circular fashion like that.
And tuck it in tightly and securely.
And this is how we prepare the greenery.
Put it in.
And next step will be the hydrangeas.
Just like that.
That's how you green your vase for the hydrangeas.